Welcome to this section.
-: Bem vindo a esta seo.
In this section we're going to look
Nesta seo, vamos
at decorators in Python.
ver os decoradores em Python.
Decorators are just higher-order functions
Decoradores so apenas funes de ordem
which return a function.
superior que retornam uma funo.
As you know, higher-order functions
Como voc sabe, funes de ordem
are functions that take in a function as an argument.
superior so funes que recebem uma funo como argumento.
And a special property of decorators
E uma propriedade especial dos
is that they must return a function as well.
decoradores  que eles devem retornar uma funo tambm.
These are used for all sorts of things.
Estes so usados para todos os tipos de coisas.
Actually, Python has some special syntax
Na verdade, o Python possui uma sintaxe especial
that allows us to use decorators
que nos permite usar decoradores
in a very easy to read manner.
de maneira muito fcil de ler.
If you've got no idea why you might want
Se voc no tem idia porque voc
to use a decorator, watch on.
pode querer usar um decorador, continue assistindo.
I'm going to give you a few examples that are really useful.
Eu vou te dar alguns exemplos que so realmente teis.
I'll see you on the next video.
Eu vou te ver no prximo vdeo.